http://www.shc.edu/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentBadgers Back 2020 - Spring Hill College's COVID-19 health and safety planning.  Click here for moreMobile NavigationOpen the navigation menuBranding SHC LogoSHC LogoYou are here:HomePrivacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyThis is the web site of Spring Hill College.The College’s postal address is: 4000 Dauphin Street Mobile, AL 36608-1791The College can be reached via e-mail at webmaster@shc.edu or you can reach us by telephone at 251-380-4000.Information Automatically Collected by the Web SiteServer LogsFor each anonymous visitor to our web site www.shc.edu, our web server automatically recognizes only the visitor’s domain name and/or IP address, but not the user’s e-mail address.We collect and survey aggregate information on what pages visitors access or visit.The information we collect is used to improve the content of our web site, and to provide you with further information about our services.CookiesWe use cookies to record user-specific information about what pages users access or visit and record session information (such as font size preference, etc…). No personal data is stored in cookies on your computer.Spring Hill College has opted in to Google Analytics Advertising features to gather non-personally identifiable information about users age, gender, and interests. This information is provided to the college via third-party cookies set by Google Analytics. This information is tracked only in aggregate form and is never used to identify individual users or gather additional information about individual users. Users can opt out of all Google Analytics tracking using the Opt-out Browser Add-onInformation Provided by the End UserEmail AddressWe collect the e-mail addresses of visitors who communicate with us via e-mail.Surveys/RegistrationsWe collect and survey aggregate information volunteered by the visitor, such as survey information and/or site registrations.Postal AddressIf you supply us with your postal address online, you will only receive the information for which you provided us your address.Phone NumberPersons who supply us with their telephone numbers online will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding programs for which they have specifically requested information.Visitor Access to the Information We CollectAccess to Consumer InformationUpon request, we provide site visitors with a description of and access to information (e.g., name, address, phone number) maintained by web site administrators about them.This information may be requested by contacting the College at the address (postal or email), aboveOpt-out PolicyIf you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail or calling us at the numbers listed above.Corrections to Personal InformationUpon request, we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information. Visitors can have this information corrected by calling us at the above telephone number.Third Party Access to the Information We CollectAd ServersWe do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies.Physical SecurityWe have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information collected from you at our site.Future Use and Visitor RecourseFuture UseFrom time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change in the future, we will post the policy changes, notifying consumers/visitors of these changes, with an opportunity to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.Visitor RecourseIf you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you should contact state or local chapters of the Better Business Bureau; state or local consumer protection offices; or the College at the address or phone number listed above.Updates to this PolicyWe may update or change this policy at any time. Your continued use of the College’s website and third party applications after any such change indicates your acceptance of these changes.AcademicsAdmissions & AidStudent LifeAbout SHCAlumniAthleticsNews & EventsClose menu
